Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES, 1921-80 (Part 2)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES (part 2)
  - BANKS
    - Justice Campaign/ Consumer Loan Funds
      - PP of Stark County, Canton, OH, 4/30/1979-11/1/1979 (Box 67, Folder 113)
      - PP Association Butler County, Hamilton, OH, 4/30/1979-8/6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 114)
      - PP of Mahoning Valley, Inc Youngstown, OH, 6/29/1978-1/23/1980 (Box 67, Folder 115)
      - PP of Bucks County Bristol, PA, 6/20/1978 (Box 67, Folder 116)
      - PP of Southeastern PA, Philadelphia, PA, 6/16/1978-4/30/1979 (Box 67, Folder 117)
      - PP of Chester County, West Chester, PA, 6/20/1978 (Box 67, Folder 118)
      - PP of Rhode Island, Providence, RI, 6/20/1978-8/11/1978 (Box 67, Folder 119)
      - PP of Central South Carolina Columbia, SC, 4/30/1979-6/12/1979 (Box 67, Folder 120)
      - PP Association Memphis, TN, 7/7/1978-1/23/1980 (Box 67, Folder 121)
      - PP Association of Nashville Nashville, TN, 6/21/1978-11/29/1979 (Box 67, Folder 122)
      - PP Cameron & Willacy Counties Brownsville, TX, 6/2/1978-7/11/1978 (Box 67, Folder 123)
      - PP Center of Houston, Houston, TX, 4/27/1979-1/24/1980 (Box 67, Folder 124)
      - PP of San Angelo, San Angelo, TX, 6/6/1978-4/11/1979 (Box 67, Folder 125)
      - PP Association of Utah, Salt Lake City, UT, 4/27/1979-10/23/1979 (Box 67, Folder 126)
      - PP of Northern Virginia Falls Church, Virginia Chapter of PP Metropolitan Washington DC, 12/10/1979 (Box 67, Folder 127)
      - Peninsula PP, Hampton VA, 11/1979 (Box 67, Folder 128)
      - PP of Tidewater, VA, Norfolk, VA, 5/8/1979-1/23/1980 (Box 67, Folder 129)
      - PP Association of Burlington, VT, 6/21/1978-1/8/1980 (Box 67, Folder 130)
      - PP Association of Wisconsin, Milwaukee, WI, 11/1/1979-2/4/1980 (Box 67, Folder 131)
  - CORRESPONDENCE GENERAL
    - Medical Dept, Stein, Francine, Abortion Loan & Tech Assistant, General Correspondence
      - 1/9/1975-11/30/1978 (Box 67, Folder 132)
      - 8/3/1973-9/11/1974 (Box 67, Folder 133)
  - Stein, F., Abortion Loan/Tech Assistant, Effect of 1st Trimester Abortion on Affiliate Income & Patient Enrollment, 11/1976 (Box 67, Folder 134)
  - Abortion Loan/Tech Assistant, Medical
    - Family Health Services of Mississippi
      - 1974 (Box 67, Folder 135)
      - 1975 (Box 67)
    - Harrisburg Reproductive Health Services, 4/14/1975-11/10/1975 (Box 67, Folder 136)
    - Ms. Carla J. Herman, Missoula, MT, 2/12/1976 (Box 67, Folder 137)
    - Knoxville Center for Reproductive Health, 9/2/1976-11/5/1976 (Box 67, Folder 138)
    - Miscellaneous Free Standing Clinics
      - 1974 (Box 67, Folder 139)
      - 1975-4/14/1977 (Box 67)
    - Preterm, Cleveland, OH
      - 9/27/1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 140)
      - 1975-1/18/1978 (Box 67)
    - Preterm, Newton, MA, 2/17/1977-2/14/1978 (Box 67, Folder 141)
    - San Vincente Hospital, CA, 7/16/1976-9/16/1976 (Box 67, Folder 142)
    - Sigma Reproductive Health Center, 10/10/1975 (Box 67, Folder 143)
    - Tallahassee Feminist Women's Health Center (4/30/1976-3/9/1978) (Box 67, Folder 144)
    - Field Dept, Stein, Francine, Abortion Loan Fund, Texas Pregnancy Control, Inc. from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 67, Folder 145)
      - 1975 (Box 67)
    - Women's Health Center of West Virginia, 10/14/1975-7/21/1978 (Box 67, Folder 146)
    - Women's Health Services, CT from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 67, Folder 147)
      - 1975-1/18/1978 (Box 67)
    - Women's Suburban Clinic, Paoli, PA, 8/26/1975 (Box 67, Folder 148)
    - Surgical Services Loan/Tech Assistant, Future Directions, Goals, 6/9/1978 (Box 67, Folder 149)
    - Abortion Loan/Tech Assistant, Medical, Loan Agreement/Security Agreement, Greenbaum, Wolff & Ernst Revised 1974, 10/2/1973-3/1/1974 (Box 67, Folder 150)
  - Stein, Francine, Abortion Loan/Technical Assistant International Abortion Projects
    - 6/23/1975-1/18/1978 (Box 67, Folder 151)
    - Australia, 1/9/1976-6/23/1977 (Box 67, Folder 152)
    - Canada, 1/11/1979-4/17/1979 (Box 67, Folder 153)
    - Colombia, 7/13/1976 (Box 67, Folder 154)
    - International Committee for Abortion Loans, 4/22/1977 (Box 67, Folder 155)
    - International, Holland, 12/28/1976 (Box 67, Folder 156)
    - IPAS (International Pregnancy Advisory Services), 1/1976-5/26/1977 (Box 67, Folder 157)
    - Malaysia, 10/10/1975 (Box 67, Folder 158)
    - Mexico, 9/18/1979-10/11/1979 (Box 67, Folder 159)
    - International Population Services Europe, The Netherlands, 8/27/1976 (Box 67, Folder 160)
    - Philippines, 10/1975 (Box 67, Folder 161)
    - New York, 8/5/1976-2/8/1977 (Box 67, Folder 162)
    - Singapore, 12/2/1975 (Box 67, Folder 163)
    - San Salvador, 1/30/1976-4/23/1976 (Box 67, Folder 164)
    - Taiwan, 10/7/1975-2/11/1976 (Box 67, Folder 165)
    - Thailand, 10/10/1975-12/8/1978 (Box 67, Folder 166)
  - Surgical Loan/Technical Ass't, Medical, Joint Ventures, Affiliate/Hospital or Other Medical Providers, 5/2/1978-8/3/1978 (Box 67, Folder 167)
  - Field Dept, Abortion Loan Fund & Tech Ass't Program, Mimeos, General
    - 10/9/1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 168)
    - 1975-2/10/1977 (Box 67)
  - SSL/TA Medical Memo, Special Meeting on Abortion Data, 5/21/1978 (Box 67, Folder 169)
  - Abortion Loan Field Dept, Non-Profit Tax Exempt Participants, 6/9/1976 (Box 67, Folder 170)
  - Abortion Loan/Tech Ass't Field, Stein, F., Preterm Physician's Manual, 7/27/1976 (Box 67, Folder 171)
  - Medical Surgical Services Loan/Tech Ass't Quarterly Report, 10/20/1977 (Box 67, Folder 172)
  - Surgical Services/Tech Ass't Medical Status Report for B & F Committee Meeting, 6/2/1978 (Box 67, Folder 173)
  - Abortion Field Dept, Stein, Francine, Status of Abortion Loan & Tech Ass't Program (Box 67)
    - 9/27/1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 174)
    - 1975 (Box 67)
  - STERILIZATION LOAN PROGRAM
    - Medical, Roff, W, AUS/PPWP Loan Fund, 1/19/1979-1/10/1980 (Box 67, Folder 175)
    - PPFA/AUS Program, Policy Committee, 10/11/1977-1/9/1980 (Box 67, Folder 176)
    - Medical, Stein, F., AUS/PPFA Loan Fund, 11/29/1976-7/10/1978 (Box 67, Folder 177)
    - PPFA/AUS Loan Fund, Medical Budget, 4/13/1978 (Box 67, Folder 178)
    - PPFA/AVS Loan, Medical International Fertility Research Program Data Systems, 11/10/1977-5/2/1978 (Box 67, Folder 179)
    - Medical, PPFA/AVS Orientation Seminar December 11-12, 1977, 10/3/1977-2/9/1978 (Box 67, Folder 180)
    - Sterilization Loan Med AVS/PPFA PPCO Minilap Training Program, 12/7/1979-4/4/1980 (Box 67, Folder 181)
    - Sterilization Loan Medical AVS/PPFA/PPAN Minilap Training Program, 3/28/1979-10/24/1979 (Box 67, Folder 182)
    - Abortion Loan/Tech Ass't Medical Status of Sterilization Loan Program, 1/26/1977-1/27/1978 (Box 67, Folder 183)
    - PPFA-AVS Sterilization Project, 4/7/1977-12/1/1977 (Box 67, Folder 184)
    - Medical, PPWP/AVS Sterilization Seminar 1977, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 185-186)
    - Sterilization Centennial Conference June, 1980 (AVS/PPFA/APPP), 11/29/1979-1/30/1980 (Box 67, Folder 187)
    - Medical, PPFA/AVS Sterilization Training Program, 11/29/1978-12/10/1979 (Box 67, Folder 188)
    - Medical, Sterilization Task Force, 1/6/1978 (Box 67, Folder 189)
    - PPFA/AVS Loan Medical United Health Services Plan, Detroit, MI, 11/21/1977 (Box 67, Folder 190)
  - AVS Loan/Tech Assistant, Medical
    - PP Birmingham Area, Birmingham, AL, 5/3/1979 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - PP of Southern Arizona, Inc. Tuscon, AZ, 6/1978 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - PPWP Los Angeles, CA, 12/8/1978 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - PP Santa Clara County, San Jose, CA, 6/15/1978 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - PP Santa Barbara, CA, 10/25/1979 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - PP North Central Florida, Gainesville Legal (Paul, Eve), 4/19/1979 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - PP NE Florida, Jacksonville, 11/7/1977-5/11/1978 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - PP Association of Southwest Florida, Sarasota, FL, 6/15/1979 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - PP Center Louisville, KY, 7/31/1978 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - PP Association of Maryland, Baltimore, 1/16/1978-6/14/1979 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Muskegon Area PP, Muskegon, MI, 1/16/1979 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - PP of Northern Nevada, Reno, NV, 6/9/1978 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - PP of Broome County, Binghamton, NY, 4/25/1978-6/7/1978 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Memphis PP Association Inc, Memphis, TN, 10/24/1977 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - PP Association of Vermont, Burlington, VT, 11/8/1978-9/27/1979 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - PP Cameron/Willacy Counties, Brownsville,TX, 2/20/1978 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Peninsula PP, Hampton, VA, 12/8/1978 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Medical Dept Abortion
    - 9/28/1978-12/11/1978 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Karman Supercoil, 2/22/1974-3/24/1974 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Risk Management Seminar in Abortion November 30- December 1, 1980 in Los Angeles, 9/10/1980 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Medical, Abortion & Medicaid
    - Legal (Paul, Eve), 3/1/1978-6/21/1979 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - 6/22/1977-8/11/1977 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - General Information (from sources other than medical dept), 3/15/1977-10/5/1979 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Medical Dept, Abortion Proposal, 5/20/1970-7/20/1970 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Medical Dept, Abortion Referrals
    - Legal from 1978 (Paul, Eve), 9/27/1978-8/22/1979 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - 10/6/1975-10/26/1979 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Abortion Referral & Civil Liability, 2/24/1976 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Medical Dept, Abortion Services: Data for Evaluation (Data Collection System), 8/24/1978-1/12/1979 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Medical Dept
    - Abortion, Physicians Training in PP Affiliates, 6/21/1979-11/1/1979 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Abortion & Sterilization Monthly Report Form, 7/1970-8/1970 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Affiliate Medical Reviews, 1/23/1976 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Agreements w/ Backup Hospitals Insurance, 1/7/1977 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Contraceptives
      - Correspondence, 4/27/1956-12/26/1973 (Box 68, Folder 33)
      - Contraceptive Methods Used by Planned Parenthood Patients, 6/5/1974 (Box 68, Folder 34)
      - Table of Contraceptive Products, circa 1973 (Box 68, Folder 35)
      - Contraceptive Products Used by PPFA Affiliates, 5/21/1975 (Box 68, Folder 36)
      - References Regarding Intrauterine Devices, circa 1976 (Box 68, Folder 37)
      - Spermacides, Suppositories, circa 1979 (Box 68, Folder 38)
      - Diaphragms, 9/6/1978-12/28/1978 (Box 68, Folder 39)
      - Diaphragms, Holland Rantos, 2/24/1977-7/27/1979 (Box 68, Folder 40)
      - Encare Oval, 10/28/1977-2/15/1979 (Box 68, Folder 41)
      - Intravaginal Device Research, 1/2/1979-6/11/1979 (Box 68, Folder 42)
      - Flavo-Cept (Nova Corporation), 9/5/1978 (Box 68, Folder 43)
      - Depo-Provera from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 68, Folder 44)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 68)
      - Intrauterine Devices
        - General Correspondence
          - 1970-1974 (Box 68, Folder 45)
          - 1975-1978 (Box 68)
        - CU-7 (Copper)
          - 1971-1974 (Box 68, Folder 46)
          - 1975-1978 (Box 68)
        - Dalkon Shield
          - 1/24/1975-4/30/1979 (Box 68, Folder 47)
          - 5/8/1974-12/24/1974 (Box 68, Folder 48)
          - 1/27/1971-6/4/1973 (Box 68, Folder 49)
          - Affiliate Correspondence, 10/21/1971-9/9/1974 (Box 68, Folder 50)
        - Hartman Fund, 4/2/1965-5/13/1966 (Box 68, Folder 51)
        - Lippes Loop, 12/18/1978 (Box 68, Folder 52)
        - Lippes Loop, Faulkner Grant from 1965
          - 1966-1974 (Box 68, Folder 53)
          - 1975 (Box 68)
        - Majzlin Spring, 11/20/1970-6/11/1973 (Box 68, Folder 54)
        - Medical Device Amendments 1973 S2368 (Kennedy Bill), 8/1973-9/1973 (Box 68, Folder 55)
        - Progestasert (Alza), 3/16/1976-4/21/1976 (Box 68, Folder 56)
        - Survey July, 1973 IUD Utilization by 42 Affiliates, 7/20/1973 (Box 68, Folder 57)
      - Oral Contraceptives
        - from 1969
          - 1969-1974 (Box 68, Folder 58)
          - 1975-1979 (Box 68)
        - Oral Benefits & Risks of Oral Contraceptives Dr. Tyler, 10/17/1978 (Box 68, Folder 59)
        - Draft of Proposed Patient Labeling for OC's, 11/21/1975 (Box 68, Folder 60)
        - Dethylstibestrol (DES) from 1971
          - 11/1971-1974 (Box 68, Folder 61)
          - 1975-1979 (Box 68)
        - Approved by FDA, circa 1966 (Box 68, Folder 62)
        - Effect on Vitamin A, 5/24/1971 (Box 68, Folder 63)
        - Oral Contraceptives & Liver Tumors, 2/27/1976 (Box 68, Folder 64)
        - Oral Low Dosage
          - 1970-1974 (Box 68, Folder 65)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 68)
        - Insurance & the Pill, British Medical Journal, 10/27/1973 (Box 68, Folder 66)
        - Post Coital Pill, 6/19/1978-10/10/1978 (Box 68, Folder 67)
        - Melamed, Dubrow Affair, 11/25/1968-8/13/1969 (Box 68, Folder 68)
        - Status Report of Long Term Enovid Users, Comments & Summary Tables, G. D. Searle & Company, 8/1/1966 (Box 68, Folder 69)
        - Enovid "25 Month Club," 10/5/1962-10/21/1966 (Box 68, Folder 70)
        - Enovid, General, 4/28/1960-4/2/1965 (Box 68, Folder 71)
        - Enovid, Surveys, Long Term Studies, 8/10/1962-11/15/1963 (Box 68, Folder 72)
        - Enovid, Food & Drug Administration, 8/8/1962-8/13/1963 (Box 68, Folder 73)
        - List of Contraceptive Products, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 74)
        - Sequential Oral, 12/23/1975-2/25/1976 (Box 68, Folder 75)
        - Prescription of Oral contraceptives, 6/1962-7/23/1968 (Box 68, Folder 76)
        - Report on the Oral Contraceptive by the Advisory Committee OB-GYN-FDA, 8/1/1966 (Box 68, Folder 77)
        - Suggested Changes in Federal Register re: OCs & Detailed Patient Labeling, 1/7/1977 (Box 68, Folder 78)
        - Teratogenicity of Oral Contraceptives, 8/28/1973 (Box 68, Folder 79)
        - History, Nelson Hearings, Background Material, 7/1957-3/4/1970 (Box 68, Folder 80)
  - Medical Committee, Correspondence
    - Medical Committee Meeting June 14-15, 1980 Monterey, CA, 5/1980 CLOSED (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence from 1969
      - 1969-1974 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 69)
  - Medical Department
    - Correspondence from 1970
      - 1970-1974 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 69)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1969 (Box 69, Folder 4-7)
    - Medical Directors/Medical Advisory Chairmen in Medical Affiliates, 12/1971-5/1973 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Medical Director Applicants, 7/1/1974-11/22/1974 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Medical Firms, 4/1977 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Input Re: The Development of Uniform Information System for PPFA, 9/15/1976 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Medical Digest, 9/1980 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Memos, Mimeos, 8/11/1975-9/1980 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Memos, Mimeos, 1970-1974 (Box 69, Folder 14-15)
    - Memos to Affiliates, 1959-1965 (Box 69, Folder 16-17)
    - Contraceptive Memos, 1957-1968, 2/9/1956-10/14/1968 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Nayagam's Alphabetically Arranged Medical Dept Memoranda, 6/29/1973 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Medical Review of Affiliates from 1969
      - 1969-1974 (Box 69, Folder 20)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 69)
    - Medical Review Program Progress Report, 5/27/1969-5/19/1970 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Proposal on Medical Reviews, 11/1975 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Medical Rights Fund
      - 2/25/1975-4/4/1979 (Box 69, Folder 23)
      - Contributions for Dr. Edelin, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 24)
      - Contributions, Memos to Ethel Ash, 3/18/1975-3/29/1977 (Box 69, Folder 25)
      - Honorary Advisory Committee Member List, circa 1975 (Box 69, Folder 26)
      - Minutes, 5/28/1975-10/11/1977 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Medical Standards & Guidelines, Correspondence, 5/31/1977-12/31/1979 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Interim Medical Standards, 6/14/1977 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Proposed Revisions & Additions to PPFA Medical Standards & Guidelines, 10/10/1979 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Medical Proposed Changes in Medical Standards, 4/30/1979 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Medical Revised Manual of Medial Standards & Guidelines, 9/6/1977 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Recommendations on Review of Affiliate Medical Programs, 9/12/1973 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Staff Meetings, 9/5/1975 (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Mothers' Letters, Procedure General, circa 1955-1962 (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Medical Dept
    - Medical, New & Nonofficial Drugs, 10/1955 (Box 69, Folder 36)
    - New Perspective in Provision of Birth Control Services (Utilizing Birth Control Services to Initiate Comprehensive Health Screening Langmyhr, M.D. & D. Stewart), 5/18/1967 (Box 69, Folder 37)
    - Physicians on PPWP Committees, 3/1974 (Box 69, Folder 38)
    - Medical Pill Purchase Program Legal from 1979 (Paul, Eve), 1/18/1979 (Box 69, Folder 39)
    - Contraceptives, Oral Pill Purchase Program
      - 3/18/1980-4/28/1980 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 70)
      - 1/11/1971-12/19/1970 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - 1/30/1968-12/31/1970 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - 12/22/1964-10/1/1967 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Affiliates Price Survey, 12/1964 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Medical Polls, 2/18/1929 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Pregnancy Testing
      - Correspondence from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 70, Folder 8)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 70)
      - Medical Oval False Claim PP Endorsement, 2/10/1972-5/31/1972 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Survey, Pregnancy Testing Materials, 4/16/1973-9/27/1973 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Pregnancy Testing Purchase Plan from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 70, Folder 11)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 70)
    - Program Guidelines for Family Planning Services Under Section 1001 Public Health Services Act, 12/22/1975 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Proposed Reorganization of Medical Dept, 9/11/1969-1/30/1970 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Provera, 5/1/1979 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Purchase Agreement RHO(D) Immune Globin (Human), 6/25/1974 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - PP Affiliates, Pill Research, 9/30/1970 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Research Projects, 8/11/1978-7/26/1979 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Research Proposals, 2/24/1966 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Reporting Non-Contraceptive Services, 8/3/1970 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - STAFF
      - Medical Consultant, Bradshaw, Lois E., 3/28/1978 (Box 70, Folder 20)
      - Bradshaw, Lois E., Chronological, 8/22/1977-3/1/1978 (Box 70, Folder 21)
      - Denniston, George, 1/14/1968 (Box 70, Folder 22)
      - Hunt, Dr. Ruth, Medical Evaluator, 10/1/1976-1/31/1979 (Box 70, Folder 23)
      - Medical Abortion Consultant, Knies, Marjorie, 10/5/1977-12/8/1978 (Box 70, Folder 24)
      - Landmyhr, George, M.D., Memos Correspondence from 1971
        - 1969-1972 (Box 70, Folder 25)
        - 1978 (Box 70)
      - Perkin, Gordon W., M.D. Associate Medical Director, 9/3/1964-3/19/1965 (Box 70, Folder 26)
      - Roff, Ellen W.
        - Program Associate, 2/28/1979-1/31/1980 (Box 70, Folder 27)
        - Chronological, 1979-1980 (Box 70, Folder 28-29)
      - Rogers, Walter, M.D., Chronological, 1969-1971 (Box 70, Folder 30)
      - Tyrer, Louise, M.D.
        - Informed Consent Forms (Paul, Eve), 12/28/1978-6/25/1979 (Box 70, Folder 31)
        - Appointment, 8/27/1975 (Box 70, Folder 32)
        - Correspondence, 6/13/1975-3/16/1981 (Box 70, Folder 33)
        - Correspondence to Medical Directors, 9/3/1975 (Box 70, Folder 34)
        - ABC TV "Close-Up on Women's Health: A Question of Survival," 1/10/1976 (Box 70, Folder 35)
        - Travel & Meeting Schedule, 7/31/1978-10/16/1978 (Box 70, Folder 36)
        - Chronological TRRV 12/1979, 5/24/1976-12/12/1979 (Box 70, Folder 37)
      - Widdecombe, Judith
        - Consultant, 1/26/1979-7/26/1979 (Box 70, Folder 38)
        - Chronological from 9/1979, 7/23/1979 (Box 70, Folder 39)
      - Wilson, Rowena, Assistant Medical Director, 7/6/1979-5/14/1980 (Box 70, Folder 40)
      - Woolf, Ralph Benson, M.D., Correspondence & Memos, 8/16/1972-1/3/1974 (Box 70, Folder 41)
    - Sterilization
      - Legal (Paul, Eve), 11/20/1978-4/9/1979 (Box 70, Folder 42)
      - Sterilization, 7/12/1976-2/12/1980 (Box 70, Folder 43)
      - Sterilization Task Force, Legal (Paul, Eve), 3/5/1979 (Box 70, Folder 44)
      - Sterilization Task Force, 1/18/1979-2/14/1979 (Box 70, Folder 45)
      - Medical Vasectomy, 3/1/1979-10/1980 (Box 70, Folder 46)
    - Summer Apprenticeship Program for Medical Students, 8/23/1970-10/22/1971 (Box 70, Folder 47)
    - 1970 Survey of Non-Contraceptive Clinical Service, 6/16/1970 (Box 70, Folder 48)
    - Venereal Diseases from 1961 (Box 70)
      - 1961-1974 (Box 70, Folder 49)
      - 1978 (Box 70)
    - Screening Strategies for Cervical Cancer & Cervical Intraepithelial Neoplasia, circa 1979 (Box 70, Folder 50)
  - Research Dept
    - Automated Patient Patient Record System
      - Annual, 1966-1968 (Box 70, Folder 51)
      - Correspondence, 1/18/1966-5/5/1971 (Box 70, Folder 52)
      - Monthly Summary, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 53)
      - Monthly, March 1967-12 months 1969 (Box 70, Folder 54)
      - Production Time Report Monthly Summary, 6/1969-7/1969 (Box 70, Folder 55)
      - Automated Record System Instructions, 3/1969 (Box 70, Folder 56)
    - Planning/Research CL-7 Statistical Report
      - Correspondence, General, 3/11/1976-4/18/1980 (Box 70, Folder 57)
      - Correspondence, General 1971-1975
        - 1971-1974 (Box 70, Folder 58)
        - 1975 (Box 70)
      - The Annual Affiliate Report, 2/27/1974 (Box 70, Folder 59)
      - 1970 CL-7 Statistical Report, 1/16/1970-10/29/1970 (Box 70, Folder 60)
      - CL-7 Affiliates Annual Report, 1/3/1966-5/8/1969 (Box 70, Folder 61)
      - Correspondence, 1/2/1962-8/3/1965 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Planning & Evaluation 1978 CL-7 Annual Report, Corrections, Definitions, & Insurance Information, 1978-6/1/1979 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - 1979 CL-7 Service Data Reporting Form Definitions & Instructions, 1/21/1980 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Planning & Evaluation 1978 CL-7 Annual Report Supplement, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Annual Report Financial Data, 2/14/1978-12/5/1978 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Affiliates Annual Report Financial Data, 1975-1978 [for years 1974-1977] (Box 71, Folder 6-9)
      - Patient Reporting 1977: NRSFPS, CL-7, 12/21/1976 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Patient Statistics
        - 1978 Forms, Checklist, Instructions, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 11)
        - 1977, 2/1979 (Box 71, Folder 12)
        - Revised, 1976, 11/1/1978 (Box 71, Folder 13)
        - 1976 (Box 71, Folder 14)
        - Average Number of Patients Per Clinic, 3/22/1976 (Box 71, Folder 15)
        - 1975, 11/5/1976 (Box 71, Folder 16)
        - 1974, 10/1975 (Box 71, Folder 17)
        - 1973, 10/4/1974 (Box 71, Folder 18)
        - Patient & Visit Statistics January 1-December 31, 1972, 8/17/1973-9/27/1973 (Box 71, Folder 19)
        - Research Note, 1972, 11/1/1973 (Box 71, Folder 20)
        - Correspondence, 1976-1977, 12/13/1976-8/17/1978 (Box 71, Folder 21-22)
        - Informatics Inc., 3/9/1978 (Box 71, Folder 23)
      - Service Data
        - Instructions Guide & Form, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 24)
        - 1975-1977, 3/9/1975-8/14/1978 (Box 71, Folder 25-27)
        - Service Data & Instruction Manual, 1974, 3/17/1975-6/27/1975 (Box 71, Folder 28)
      - Miscellaneous, 1958-1969 (Box 71, Folder 29)
      - Western Region, 3/1973-8/1973 (Box 71, Folder 30)
      - Southwest Region, 3/1973-10/1973 (Box 71, Folder 31)
      - Midwest Region, 3/1973-4/1973 (Box 71, Folder 32)
      - Great Lakes Region, 3/1973-7/1973 (Box 71, Folder 33)
      - Southeast Region, 4/1973-11/1973 (Box 71, Folder 34)
      - Mid-Atlantic Region, 3/1973-7/1973 (Box 71, Folder 35)
      - Northeast Region, 3/1973-7/1973 (Box 71, Folder 36)
      - CL-7's 1972, 7/19/1973 (Box 71, Folder 37)
      - Western Region, 3/1972-8/1972 (Box 71, Folder 38)
      - Southwest Region, 3/1972-5/1972 (Box 71, Folder 39)
      - Midwest Region, 2/1972-4/1972 (Box 71, Folder 40)
      - Great Lakes Region, 2/1972-5/1972 (Box 71, Folder 41)